Hello hi guys welcome back to my channel
in today's video I am going to tell you that
if your scooter or bike meets with an accident and gets
damaged a lot, then
how can you get clean insurance for it.
This video is going to be made keeping in mind all of you
because I had made a video in
which I had told that you can
gift a bike online sitting at home,
how can you do this sitting at home, you people have
commented a lot on that video and asked, tell me how to
take insurance claim in this way,
tried to take insurance claim, what happens,
how much percentage do we get, tell me about the whole process,
so finally an incident happened with us here
which you
can see was accepted, so I had an accident with my scooter
and you can see here that a
lot of information got deleted in my scooter, you
can see this, on the left side the
veena of my scooter and you can see here that the
indicator is broken, okay this is going to be completely changed,
you can see it here, there is
Kashi Express here itself, you
can see some music of this, it has been completed.  There will be a
change
and at the same time you can also see the stand, the
stand is also like this you
can see the footrest, this is fine and nothing has happened here
because all this happens
outside, after this his wife, so
let's quickly go to the
service center of Amma TVS and we will find out here
and see what he tells us,
okay, whatever details there are, I am going to
tell you all about it in the video, if
you should see it, so that you remain clear
and I will tell you the entire process, from
depositing my scooter till
when do I get the delivery after completion, till then, how much did
I have to spend, how much I am going to
cover everything in this video,
so let's go to the
service center, so here we
can reach the service
center of TVS, now we will see here and
talk to some staff here who can
tell me the entire process, so let's go
and do this and see,
ah
you come now,
after all, let's go here, we are with ma'am  Let's
talk about the insurance claim
process and how much
time it will take and
what will be the payment system, we will know all these things
in this video, so please do it, please send it
to Kushwaha police station first of all
and the name is required, we will ask Kiran
all the details Meghnad is a scooty and whose house has once been occupied by a
student and I want to
take it to the police station and what is it like in today's date, it is a
digital world, so what do people do, they
search on the internet and go to China
Sea, they think that my work is house,
so I thought, then share it with the millions of people present in this video,
so this is known to you, through this
insurance claim,
first of all, and then what will happen, right now,
like I have brought you a scooty,
please if you slide something and
say there is a problem, I will
tell you this message, what should I do, comment, like if we
talk about the documents, then the first
question is what is your mind, yes, okay, okay, if the
police took the above, then all these things which
madam told, all these things which I will make reach the
district magistrate, you
can easily note the support  Okay,
you can do it by making the village Su,
so I will solve it for you and what will be the profit after this,
I have given you all this paper and after this we will do this
process, then how much time will it take,
play the song after the inauspicious rock band births, do the
latest research company, do it
within two days for my 3
people, I have to take 15 days for that, that
expenses,
11,
okay yes, the jewellery is simple, if you
give it here and if
you have all the papers complete, it gets completed here in two days
and when will the payment be made,
I have given the insurance company statement,
then we have to give it, it is
proved for maximum times, this is
in the house, that is, to
three companies, Pankaj, here,
say that the bill of the world is made for this, for
whatever part is charged here, for
the time being, you will have to do the font, how do you want to return it,
how do you want to return it through credit card or whatever,
and after that the
process will come to you in minimum 5 days and
after that, maximum 15 days, it will be credited to
your account within 15 days  I have that which will be
deposited, those points will be given to the company
Eros, okay, so let's do this, we
hand over the scooter to them and today I am not fasting, I will not
smoke or drink, only the day is 24th
February, you please note it down, okay, today on 24th
February I am going to deliver the car here
and after that we will see how much time it takes
us to take the car here,
and at the same time I will tell you
how many days it took me to clear the insurance claim, our insurance customs, so let's do the
programs here
and take care of the remaining half of the
problems, we will take delivery of the car on
time, how much did we have to pay
or did we have to
spend more on these, finally today
our scooter is ready, we will
call from the service center, how do you want to take your scooter today, so
let's go to the service center
and see
how much more expenses we have there, and friend, let me
tell you that the scooter is there, I had given it
for claim, I had deposited it here on 24th February
and also the person who  I am going to
get my degree, today's
date is four months from here, that is, eight months, so
in this whole process, the service center
people are not at fault, it
depends on the insurance person, the
insurance person gives your approval
in one day, if they say something wrong, then
you will go in two-three days and
get it cleared, so it takes
time for approval, so let's talk about all the things, first of all I will take
delivery of the scooter
and see how much it costs, but I have
reached the service
center in the morning, this reference guy,
what has happened, now come
here,
if it is done, we will see about our correct bill, after
going home we
should have talked to you in detail,
how much time did everything take, so when we talked,
come and stand near me, it will be complete,
you are very stylish, it will take time,
looking at me, the loss was that the
customer did not have complete information about the insurance company, was
not aware of the obscene people, if the customer wants to
buy a scooter, he should have complete knowledge, then get
your work done quickly  You may be surprised that this
file is created and goes to the insurance company
and the register is reduced. I'm sorry, the
survey has to be done within an hour,
that the survey will be done within 72 hours,
because of Saturday and Sunday holidays, it gets washed away, the
reason is that it is late, so the
channel has no difference from your side in this, the
sugar actor plain mode, his
debit which has been withing a week, he
visited the service center, that he will have to come
during working hours except holidays, if he does not
come then he will have to take the toll free number, then
talk to him and tell him till then, that means if
you take this time then here you can go to the
service center for your
penis, there is no problem from there, the
problem arises, you have to contact the company, till when will you
go to the office, this person who will try, will have to
request for F1,
somewhere there, a few days and it depends,
the sooner the approval comes and the sooner
your scooter starts working, so
actually I had a
call and then
I talked to the insurance guy
through a small online video,
petrol kiss on elephant video  Mix it properly
and cover it and send the photo, then you must have taken your photo and
sent it on WhatsApp, then they have given up, so
okay, let's go and talk
about all the information and the rest we will go home, first of all
we will buy a scooty from here, so how much
time will you have to spend in my scooty, it has a
central tank, the
police have put
28, so many in it, which is broken, so how much will
I get in it, right now
you need 6a,
this is not a share of all this, that is,
how much percent is there in the termite lick,
like what problem occurs in it, like in this,
wanted list will go or cigarette,
you will take 299 plus and a
good, good link will come that
we will come back after dying, it is good,
take it to Justin's number, now
I have given you the account details,
in how many days the account statement will be
transferred to me, if you forget it, you will do it
in two days, I will
recommend you right now and this belt will be forwarded to
them, do this work a little
till now, okay, the
Fifth signs to the committee head  Pusharam, the
change has been done, I had increased the
increase, the
fifth one was cut and I will take it
[music], it has been done, tell
Ajay that the
above mentioned thing, see our scooter is completely complete
and
if I face any problem with the driver then I will take it back to the
service centre, okay and when you
come to me, I will get the bill, exactly the
same, the
list of all the things that have been put in it is here and there is commando tax,
rest there is nothing on it that you can
dry off, so finally you must have understood well in this video,
how can you take term insurance claim by buying the scooter and
what processes have to be followed,
so if you have any kind of confusion in your mind, any question in
your mind, you
can tell me by commenting in the comment section below this video so
that I can give a proper reply to it, okay
and I will try my best to explain to you properly whatever your
questions are,
so
now we wait for our channel
When does it take for the credit to be credited to our account?
We will clear this video here itself
and when I get the payment
for your insurance, I will make another video at that time
and then the
problem will be resolved.
How many days will it take for the insurance claim to develop
in the market? Okay, so let's see that's all for now
in this video. Thank you for watching Baba.